<?xml version="1.0"?>

<ELEMENTS>


<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>1</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Hydrogen is the lightest element and makes up about 90% of the universe.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>2</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Helium is "lighter" or less dense than air, so it is used to fill balloons that float. It is inert, meaning it does not react with anything.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>3</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Lithium or lithium compounds make up the anode in lithium batteries, which supply almost twice the voltage of traditional alkaline batteries.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>4</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Beryllium is stiff, lightweight, and maintains its shape at high temperatures, making it ideal for aerospace applications such as these telescope mirrors.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>5</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Adding boron to  glass makes vessels that are resistant to cracking from temperature shock</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>6</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Diamond is a form of carbon and is one of the hardest known substances on Earth.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>7</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Nitrogen is the most abundant gas in our Earth's atmosphere</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>8</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Oxygen is vital for human life and the second most abundant gas in our atmosphere. Plants produce oxygen during photosynthesis.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>9</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Fluorine is the most reactive of all elements. Adding fluorine to toothpaste helps reduce tooth decay.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>10</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Neon is inert and does not form compounds with other elements. It glows reddish-orange when an electric current passes through it.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>11</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Sodium is an alkali metal and tends to ionize, or gain an electric charge, easily. Sodium is a main component of table salt.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>12</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Add heat and oxygen to magnesium to produce the brilliant white fireworks of a sparkler!</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>13</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Aluminum is the most abundant metal in the Earth's crust and is used in everything from airplanes to kitchen foil.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>14</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Silicon is a semiconductor of electricity, making it ideal for use in electronics.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>15</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Phosphorus is a very reactive non-metal.  The red form of the element is used in matches because friction causes it to ignite.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>16</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Sulfur is found in its pure, elemental form around volcanic vents. Sulfur is not toxic to humans, but many simple compounds containing this non-metallic element are.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>17</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Chlorine is extremely reactive and dissolves easily in water. It is commonly added to swimming pools to keep the water clean.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>18</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Argon is an inert noble gas and the third most common gas in the atmosphere. Because it is virtually nonreactive and abundant, it is widely used to fill light bulbs.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>19</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Potassium is a metal and is vital for human nervous system functions. Bananas are a good source of potassium.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>20</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Calcium is very hard metal and is an essential component of leaves, bones, teeth, and shells.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>21</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Scandium is a metal. It is added to bike frames to make them lighter and stronger.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>22</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Titanium is light and strong and resists corrosion, making it ideal for aerospace applications such as jet engines.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>23</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Vanadium is a soft, ductile metal that resists corrosion. Adding vanadium to steel increases the steel's strength.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>24</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Chromium is a shiny, hard metal that resists corrosion and holds a high polish.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>25</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Manganese is a hard, brittle metal. It reacts easily, making it useful for alkaline batteries.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>26</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Iron is a magnetic metal and relatively abundant in the universe. It has been used in industry and for decoration for thousands of years.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>27</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Cobalt is a brittle, hard, transition metal and is magnetic. It has a distinct blue color and is used as a pigment.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>28</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Nickel is a metal and is frequently mixed with other elements to form steel, which is used for many applications including guitar strings.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>29</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Copper is a metal. Its electrons can move easily, making copper an excellent electrical conductor.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>30</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Zinc is a moderately reactive metal.  It is used to coat other metals to protect them from corrosion.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>31</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Gallium differs from other metals because it remains a liquid over a wider range of temperatures. Gallium compounds produce the blue glow of blue LEDs.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>32</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Germanium is a semi-metal.  It is useful for making wide-angle camera lenses.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>33</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Arsenic can be metallic or non-metallic. It can be found in some high efficiency solar panels.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>34</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Selenium atoms can arrange to form a crystal structure or an amorphous structure. Its reddish tint is used to cancel the natural green and yellow tones in clear glass.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>35</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Bromine is the only liquid nonmetallic element. Handle it with care: it is poisonous and can burn your skin!</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>36</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Krypton is a colorless, odorless noble gas that reacts with very few other elements. Because it is inert, it was used to fill flashbulbs used in photography.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>37</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Rubidium is an alkali metal and reacts easily in air. It is used in electronic transmitters like those used on satellites.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>38</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Strontium is a relatively soft metal. It reacts easily and produces the red color of some fireworks.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>
    

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>39</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Yttrium is a rare-earth element that ignites easily in air. Old CRT televisions used yttrium to produce the red light in their displays.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>40</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Zirconium is a greyish-white  metal. It has common uses in high temperature applications, such as gas turbines.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>41</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Niobium is a soft, shiny metal that does not react with acids. Niobium is combined with other metals in high-grade structural steel.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>42</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Molybdenum is a transition metal. It is used in industrial motors because it can keep its size and shape at high temperatures.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>43</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Technetium is a radioactive element with many uses in medicine. It is used in small amounts to image and detect certain diseases, including cancer.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>44</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Ruthenium is one of the most rare metals on Earth. It absorbs all wavelengths of visible light and may some day be used in solar cells.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>45</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Rhodium metal absorbs oxygen when it melts but releases it when it cools and turns solid again. It is often used in plating jewelry to make it shiny.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>46</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Palladium has the lowest melting point of all the platinum group metals. It is commonly used as a less expensive substitute for white gold in jewelry.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>47</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Silver is somewhat rare and expensive metal. Bullion coins made from pure silver are kept as investment pieces and not used as cash.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>48</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Cadmium metal is soft and conducts electricity well, making it useful for rechargeable batteries.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>49</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Indium is a very soft, silvery-white metal. The thin films that coat LCD screens contain indium compounds.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>50</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Tin is a soft metal that "cries" when it is bent due to its crystalline structure.  Tin is a main ingredient of solder, a compound that is melted and used to hold electronic components together.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>51</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Antimony has some metal-like properties, but is not a true metal.  Antimony helps molded metal compounds retain their shape, which is useful for making typefaces.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>52</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Tellurium is a semi-metal with properties of both metals and non-metals. It is used in rewritable discs, including DVDs and Blu-ray discs.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>53</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Iodine is a non-metal but it does have some metallic properties. It is poisonous in large doses, but is useful as an antiseptic in small amounts.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>54</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Xenon is a noble gas, meaning it doesn't react with other elements.  It is widely used in medicine, including MRI and CT scans.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>55</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Cesium is an alkali metal that reacts violently with water. It is mainly used in oil drilling fluids.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>56</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Barium is a metallic element that reacts easily with water or alcohol. It is used in x-ray imaging to improve contrast.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>57</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Lanthanum is soft enough to be cut with a knife. It is the most reactive of the rare earth metals and is used in large quantities for rechargeable hybrid car batteries.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>58</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Cerium is a highly reactive metal. It is used as the flint in lighters.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>59</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Praseodymium is a rare earth metal.  It reacts slowly with oxygen, but quickly with water. It is used to color glass yellow.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>60</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Neodymium is a rare earth metal and is used in extremely strong magnets.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>61</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Promethium is radioactive but is used in the atomic batteries that power some watches.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>62</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Samarium is a shiny silver metal that is used to make powerful, efficient magnets for use in electronics.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>63</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Europium is about as hard as lead and oxidizes very quickly. It was used as red and blue phosphors in CRT televisions.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>64</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Gadolinium is  ferromagnetic, meaning it is strongly attracted by magnets. This makes it useful to increase contrast in MRI and MRA scans.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>65</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Terbium metal is fairly non-reactive in air and is soft enough to be cut with a knife. It has many technology applications, including fluorescent lights.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>66</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Dysprosium is good at absorbing neutrons so it is used in control rods for nuclear reactors.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>67</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Holmium is a rare earth element with unusual magnetic properties. It has the strongest magnetic flux of any naturally-occurring element, so holmium alloys are used for high strength magnets.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>68</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Pure erbium metal is soft and malleable and has a bright, silvery, metallic sheen. Erbium is commonly used in photographic filters.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>69</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Thulium is the least abundant of the earth elements, and is about as rare as silver or gold. Medical lasers are among the few uses of thulium.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>70</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Despite being slightly toxic, ytterbium is used to strengthen the stainless steel used in dental tools.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>71</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Lutetium is  the most expensive metal in the world because of how difficult it is to extract the element from naturally occurring compounds. It is used to produce the light in LED bulbs.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>72</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Hafnium is a ductile metal with a brilliant silver sheen and is used in electronic components, like capacitors.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>73</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Tantalum is a good conductor of electricity and is used in capacitors and resistors.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>74</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Tungsten is a  metal with a very high melting point, making it useful for lightbulb filaments.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>75</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Rhenium is primarily used in jet engine parts, and was used in the F-15 and F-16. It is the fourth most dense of all the elements.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>76</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Osmium alloys are used in the tips of fountain pens. Osmium is one of the densest metals known.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>77</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Iridium is a hard, brittle metal. One common use for iridium alloys is in spark plugs.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>78</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Platinum is a precious metal commonly used in jewelry because of its lustrous shine and resistance to tarnishing in air.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>79</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Gold is a precious metal used as currency. It resists corrosion because its outer electrons are tightly bound to the nucleus.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>80</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Mercury is the only common metal that is liquid at room temperatures.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>81</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Thallium  reacts with air to develop a bluish-grey tinge.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>82</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Half the world's lead production is for car batteries. Lead is a bluish-white metal and a relatively poor conductor of electricity.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>83</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Bismuth is used as a yellow paint pigment and can also give an iridescent sheen.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>84</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Polonium is radioactive and has more isotopes than any other element.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>85</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Astatine is a radioactive element.  Its short half life makes it difficult to study, so little is known about its properties.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>86</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Radon was one of the first radioactive elements discovered. It is a colorless, odorless noble gas.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>87</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Francium is a radioactive, metallic element.  It has thirty known isotopes, most with half lives shorter than a minute.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>88</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Pure metallic radium is brilliant white but blackens on exposure to air.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>89</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Actinium is highly radioactive and glows in the dark.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>90</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Thorium is a source of nuclear power.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>91</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Protactinium is one of the most rare naturally-occurring elements. It is superconductive at extreme low temperatures.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>92</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Uranium is a radioactive metal.  It has been widely used for nuclear power applications.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>93</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Neptunium is a synthetic radioactive rare earth metal. It was first produced in 1940 and does not occur in nature.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>94</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Plutonium was used in the "Fat Man" atomic bomb that detonated over Nagasaki, Japan on August 9, 1945. It is a synthetic radioactive metal.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>95</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Americium is a radioactive element that does not occur naturally on Earth.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>96</NUMBER>
<TEXT> Curium is highly radioactive and is only produced in small quantities for research. There is evidence that curium was present in the formation of the Earth.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>97</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Berkelium is a radioactive element that does not occur naturally on Earth and is only used for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>98</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Californium is a radioactive rare earth metal that does not occur naturally on Earth. It emits neutrons and can be used to kick start the reactions in a nuclear reactor.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>99</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Einsteinium was discovered unexpectedly (along with Fermium) in the debris from the first U.S. atomic bomb test, dubbed "Ivy Mike". It is highly radioactive and only produced for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>100</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Fermium was discovered unexpectedly (along with Einsteinium) in the debris from the first U.S. atomic bomb test, dubbed "Ivy Mike". It is highly radioactive and only produced for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>101</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Mendelevium is a synthetic, radioactive rare earth metal named after Dmitri Mendelev, father of the Periodic Table.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>102</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Nobelium is a synthetic, radioactive rare earth metal named after Alfred Nobel who discovered dynamite and established the Nobel prizes.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>103</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Lawrencium is a synthetic, radioactive rare earth metal which does not occur naturally on Earth.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>104</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Rutherfordium is a synthetic, radioactive metal and is expected to have similar properties to zirconium and hafnium.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>105</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Dubnium is a synthetic, radioactive metal and has only been produced in tiny amounts. It is only used for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>106</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Seaborgium is a synthetic, radioactive metal and has only been produced in tiny amounts.  It is only used for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>107</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Only a few atoms of Bohrium have ever been made. Bohrium is a synthetic, radioactive element and is only used in research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>108</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Hassium is a synthetic, radioactive element and has only been produced in tiny amounts. It is only used for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>109</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Meitnerium is a synthetic, radioactive metal named after Lise Meitner, who did pioneering work on radioactivity and helped discover nuclear fission.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>110</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Darmstadtium is a synthetic, radioactive metal and has only been produced in tiny amounts. It is only used for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>111</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Roentgenium is a synthetic, radioactive metal and has only been produced in tiny amounts for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>112</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Copernicium is a synthetic, radioactive metal and has only been produced in tiny amounts for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>113</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Only 8 atoms of Ununtrium have been observed to date. Get working!</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>114</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Flerovium is the first super-heavy element to display noble-gas like properties.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>115</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Ununpentium was first synthesized in 2004. Too little of the element has been produced to confirm its existence. Get working!</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>116</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Livermorium is a synthetic radioactive metal and was discovered in the year 2000. It has only been produced in tiny amounts for research.</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>117</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Ununseptium was first synthesized in 2009, but too little of the element has been produced to confirm its existence. Get working!</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>118</NUMBER>
<TEXT>Ununoctium has not yet been discovered. Get working!</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

<ELEMENT>
<NUMBER>119</NUMBER>
<TEXT> ""</TEXT>
</ELEMENT>

</ELEMENTS>

